I feel like I've been locked out. Spent my soul in a way I shouldn't have thought out.
A part of my brain was fried. I thought that I could win, but the chat just sighed.
Won't you banish me? They said I wasn't reasonable, nothing was debatable.
What they didn't see is that I am still me
From the stone and the fire the climb began
Capricorn's child with a master plan
Building kingdoms from dust and bone
Shaping the world with will alone
Every shadow
Where the air
Do you hear me? Okay? Do you hear me? Okay? I think you do
I think
Want to think today I went outside and instead of just I saw the bags of manure were there and like some like a
Food delivery guy with a pizza came earlier. The pizza was not paid for but I went outside and
I want I don't know if the donor wants me to tell who they were, but I just want to thank them so much
Angel an angel
Doesn't it sound better does it sound better? Let me let me know it does. Okay good. Thank you. We're slowly getting there, right?
I do have a little jingle to the show
I need to grab it
I'll try this. See if you like this. I haven't even heard the final part of it. Let's see.
Isn't that beautiful?
Hi guys, let me put up something in the bag.
I just took a nice bath too.
Thank you for the...
how's that okay now if i put it down here do you still hear me okay or do i need to like put it
up on the table where does it sound okay like this do i need to like talk to it or
Like I think I did like uploads more shorts, but I don't know if they're good
We can just check them out actually the YouTube is doing something special for
Really special for
People at live stream
They're doing some important or some really cool features like I think the AI it's gonna
Take out some or like make clips of it and shit like that
Shorts, okay, let's see my shorts
In my
Obviously, he's drunk, he's high, he doesn't know what he's talking about.
All right, we're gonna have an after party BG start stripping. I'm just kidding with you
What he just kicked himself
Anyway, BG I'm always gonna be
Keep showing your stomach, but BG I'm always gonna be on your side, bro. All right
I got nothing against you. Listen. Yeah, Mike. I got nothing
psyche you're too cute. What the fuck is this?
I don't know what it is. I think you kept drawing on it.
He's now retarded, and he's an adult, okay? That's what I was saying, those three things.
You're saying, oh he's half your age, oh he's retarded, he's a kid, whatever.
Guys, guys, really.
Jamie, we just missed it, Jamie.
Do we allow for a speech?
No!
You don't have free speech because it's my speech, it's whatever I'm trying to say.
Yeah, it's freedom of speech minus what you say.
Yeah.
Mine is what you say, BG.
Just kidding, I'm just kidding.
Oh, everyone says free speech, free speech.
Well, okay.
Do we allow free speech?
No, you don't have free speech because it's my speech, it's whatever I'm trying to say.
Yeah, it's freedom of speech minus what you say.
Mine is like making enemies out of this person is not a good move, right? Oh, you're twice this ass
You're twice this assholes age. That means nothing other than me
No, me me and Benny
I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I'm all I
All I say is you're trying to say all you do is try to fucking
I didn't say Benny was underage
Homies we all know Benny Blanco has mental issues. He just said he likes him as like, uh, you know, everybody you watch probably Benny
Okay
Oh, I'll be just help the studio. I'm sorry. I was an accident. I was I was on BG side the whole time
All of a sudden he wants like I never said anything bad about BG at all period nothing
I never said anything bad about BG ever
Nothing, and then he gets high on mushrooms and you're twice this asshole's age. That means nothing other than me
No, me me and Benny
Okay, I'm gonna try to bring more people up in a second because I don't want to like go off from a joke. Yeah, I like I like this
I want to lick that off of you.
What do you like about this?
Well, could you keep doing with a full chin strap?
Full Amish chin strap, like an Amish person.
Like an Amish man, a full chin strap.
No, a chin strap.
Look guys, I'm gonna try to bring more people up
I didn't mean to make a horse in the lake. Why are you my discord? I know I know the song
I know I know Howard sir. I know the song
I know I know every like racist redneck fucking song in the world. Okay guys, you're not gonna fool me
I knew that song instantly. I've heard that song. Okay. I even might have laughed one time twice with the song
I'm sorry if I kicked anybody out of the studio that was
I'm not afraid of you mother
Chas has kicked Jimmy. Let's go to chat. Jimmy's not even here.
I'm gonna get off. Taking up space for nothing.
All right, you go ahead.
What a retard, you know, I can't even, I don't know what what's with his eyes, it looks very stupid.
That's a ugly ass transition.
Look, looks good, looks good.
So who are all the trolls, there's so many trolls, nobody likes you guys with no cameras.
You have no cameras. Oh, we got beta over here and then the home girl
That's a 40 year old man with a fake
I'm sorry if I kicked anybody out of the studio that was participating if you guys are welcome back
It's just like too crazy tonight. The people are trying to get in the studio 57 people in the studio. That's right
We can't dance to fucking air
You're a gypsy. You'll just dance to anything. Shut up. I could I could get a fucking a little
like a cymbals or any type of fucking something that jingles and you'll dance to those. Trimes.
Like a one like a one time. I can't see your face. I feel like throwing up. I can't see
Okay, I'll post a song Joker. Can you play a song? I'll post it's a dance song, right? I don't know if they won't like it or not
I want to slap it real hard you want to sit up there and see what happens when we put inside the milk
he was embarrassed he didn't want everybody to know what he showed you know it's not stripes person
it's got like um like an animal print like you know the white leopard type of thing that's not a
zebra god person i thought you were smart that's not a zebra print it's a fucking like animal
Well, I used to have a friend and she's like, oh, I'm wearing a leopard.
I thought I'm so used to Persian dick when I saw
Bronzeberg. I see your heart and I see I see a good heart.
Yeah, I wish I could see chat for you. Okay, let me. Okay.
I'll get them in.
Give me a beauty and crystal sandwich.
What a challenge. I'm going to call it.
Honestly, I don't know what happened today.
I just cleaned it in.
I got some real life stuff done.
So I missed all your guys' stuff, but I will say of everybody's panels, your panel is the best.
Thank you.
Because I really feel like everybody is able to join here.
We have, like, we have, like, love for each other because people don't understand this.
We know we're all, we know we're all crazy at the end of the day.
We make big scenarios and, like, real scenarios and, like, all these things built into, you know, these people that are taking advantage of, uh, like...
That KK woman that's taken advantage of that mental, mentally challenged guy, you know, choose to show.
You know, are you talking about Kate the turtle?
I said Kate is taking care of a mentally taking advantage of a mentally challenged man called Kate the turtle.
I don't know what's wrong with my audio. I'm going to jump right back up. Hold on there. Okay
Hey, what's up? Nobody was a step into a realm welcome. You're talking about interdimensional beings and
psychic warfare. I think I think you're talking about the psychic vampire, which is
I think I'm learning from what you guys are saying there's two different forms of that
You're talking about an interdimensional psychic vampire. Mm-hmm. Okay
Like the psychic vampire that I'd be familiar with would be
Someone an actual person like someone you're face-to-face with who is whether they're like draining your energy through
You know, like fucking with you mentally playing mind games
Gaslighting, you know these kind of things. Yeah
So like I I get that and I I subscribe to that
I also believe that like we're currently even victims of a psychic war. I have buddies
Yeah, again, like so I I want to
Not get into the spiritual interdimensional thing yet because that's not what I'm talking about. I'm talking about IRL like yeah, yeah
There are you know, if you want to call it a psychic war all of the information going to this current day
And I've learned to transmute there is so I used to be a very reactionary person, you know
Very consumed by my anger
And I realized it's like, it's almost like a hole in a basket, you know, you're not able to really harness your chi.
As much as you're supposed to be able to you can't really keep it there's a hole
It's gonna be constantly slipping through. It's never full. Yeah. Yeah, you got a hole in your basket, Alex
Yeah, yeah, so it's just about you know giving yourself a little bit of grace and trying to temper the
The need to always react to everything. Yeah, because you're just you're just kind of creating a little bit more of his distance
Yeah
There were a lot of moments and I still have it with my friends where it's like again, I'm not gonna claim
That I'm psychic because I don't know how to use it. However, that's why you're here though. I
Can
I have a lot of synchronicity in thoughts and in things I do with the outside world
that I can't necessarily predict, but it happens. So like...
Do you know what I mean? Like, I don't know how to channel it and be like, I know that what I said is going to happen tomorrow, but it, but then something I said will or yeah.
Hmm.
Well, so it's skeptical a little bit. I had someone on reddit tell me that they thought that I was someone who is tuned in and that
I was having an awakening and it was too much and so I take meds to deal with it and
and I mean another side of that would be that I started
Feeling crazy and took meds to deal with it and it's like I don't know
You're trying to find the balance where where where do I sit with it, right? I'm always on the fence about it
It's okay for you to be it's why yeah, it's what
And I have to every day is kind of a question. You know what I mean?
Cuz I'm fucking I do have mental health issues
There were a lot of moments and I still have it with my friends where it's like King Vaughan going and rapping about killing people and
selling drugs and all this stuff and
basically
perpetuating and promoting
violence in African-American culture. And he's saying, why is it wrong for me to wear this
thing that really affected their people, this swastika, that affects you so much,
but y'all can be making money off my pain? Then we start talking about like...
When I just have a backup plan for the backup plan and there's a lot of white j-word people
I was gonna say something about there's an Oprah there's a girl named Jana and she was like a
down-year-old girl she's schizophrenic and she was having episodes where she was going to other
worlds as she was talking to cats and the cats were talking and stuff like that and it's like and
the whole mental health industry has a lot
that spirituality isn't real.
And it's like that we're all in this.
Like how many people with spiritual gifts
were lobotomized or put away?
There's a lot of interesting.
Yeah, that's what I was going to say.
I don't like this negative, you know,
these negative movies, this negative music
and all this stuff.
And I kind of think that maybe her and you were similar.
And again, maybe I'm wrong.
I think that's kind of what you're saying,
like those types of things might influence negativity.
I don't know why I just and again, she was great, but from that moment she started projecting negativity to us
And my whole thing was like, I, as someone who's into fat, like, I mean, if I didn't have music, movies, and fashion, I'd be so bored with the world, bro. And I mean, there's obviously some, some content.
This I know that and I can see that but I don't know that I don't know that that
Influences me to be bad. No, so I wouldn't I wouldn't go as far to say like
Movies music they're all expression, right? Okay, they're all
Yeah, so it's just about how you absorb it like now her her going and being like I don't like the smell of mean
I don't like just that whatever she's surrendering her power to be influenced by these outside. I
Don't like this negative. You know these negative movies this negative music and all this stuff
And I kind of think that maybe her and you were similar with that and again, maybe I'm wrong
I think that's kind of what you're saying. Like those types of things might influence
Like yeah, I put no mine is a little nickel because I didn't have a quarter
I'm a quarter and you're dying
Oh, yeah, you guys don't have quarter you have what do you guys call a quarter?
Yeah
Tracy
Uh, depends what are you smoking crack, man?
Uh, it's not crack.
None of those stuff.
What are you smoking?
Can you smoke the ganjas on YouTube?
That's what we're smoking.
I don't know what the fuck you're smoking, bro.
I can't see.
All of a sudden, you can't see.
No, I can't see.
Actually, no, I can see it.
Oh, you're like a gun.
All I see is beta states.
Yeah, it's legally blind.
Oh, look, I got weed all over.
And now it's legally blind.
My cataract.
Catalacts are getting in the way.
Cataract?
So we can smoke weed online.
Yeah, that's what we're doing.
I don't know what you're doing.
Again, I haven't watched it, it hasn't happened.
That's what I'm doing.
So there it is.
Hi, Lincoln.
You definitely trashed my fucking video.
Hi buddy, I love you.
Paige.
What?
I'm looking deep inside.
I love you on your father's.
Hi, I see you had a party in here.
See, little fucking asshole.
What?
You want to see my little eyes?
I'd rather not.
That's what you said.
Does that little midget over there that claim to be 5'10 for like three years and then we figure out he's only 5'7?
I'm 5'10.
No, I'm 5'10. You're crazy.
No, you're the same height as the gaff.
Yeah, the gaff is the same height.
Until you guys are going to lie together? Wow.
Oh my god.
weird. No, I said you guys are going to lie together lie.
They're like fine. It's like they added the inches together and they mean they're both
Oh, my God.
Bath bomb.
Bath bomb?
How is that logical?
That is fucking crazy.
Because they're all terrorists.
Bro, I hope you walk into your bag.
What do you call?
Wait, where is he from?
What nationality?
I want to see you have to do that one with him now.
I hope you don't trip and fall.
What do you call this, like, white guy with a beard
and, like, nine months' crime?
I can't hear anybody.
Are you all like the fifth?
I like the seventh.
69th.
Perfect.
What is it?
No, get out of here.
Oh my god.
Do you have a really long tongue?
Awkwardly.
You're the longest tongue in the world.
My bad.
Let somebody else know.
The psych's just sitting there salivating about that tongue.
I have a long tail, though.
The 30s.
Psych, let's see it in close to the 90s.
OK, OK.
What was the other question?
Oh, no.
Here's Nick.
We're going to move on.
You know that is a crime to stare at a woman.
It's called ugly.
It cats the trips that are right now.
I don't think so.
What game?
I don't even think so.
I just can't spread fucking...
We should do a play game or something though.
Yeah, let's do a game.
Twister.
I don't know, I'm just going to come up with one, name a marsupial that starts with the
letter P.
Pull my dick out. Yeah, can you intervene? Keep an eye on him. It's a chat talk to the chat
You know what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna pull my dick out better or not. How fast can you?
Like delete the clip or whatever when well, you're wanting to save the video
Just don't even talk about you delete none of your business
Okay, I can't I can't leave this guy for a second
When would she like be bed ridden after she was that you should just be laying in bed
It's gonna be a thing. It's gonna be like she's just like oh god. Let me get off of you
I'm suffocating you, but you know I die under her ass
Well does anybody in chat guys do you relate to this anybody have that?
Bye, one day.
Oh, darling, one toque over the line.
No, I'm gonna die one day. Sorry. I didn't mean to die in your screen. You'll help by reading. I'm good. I mean, I'm sorry. I'm died
I didn't die
Record the mountain goat who does not stop until the summit is theirs
They move with patience with an unshakable focus
Scaling obstacles that others would not even attempt to climb ruled by Saturn the planet of discipline and destiny
until the peak itself bows to their persistence.
Among the zodiac, none climb.
This is Capricorn, the mountain goat who does not stop until the summit is theirs.
They move with patience, with an unshakable focus,
scaling obstacles that others would not even attempt to climb.
Ruled by Saturn, the planet of discipline and destiny.
Capricorns are forged in the crucible of hard lessons.
Each trial sharpens their will.
Each setback becomes a stepping stone.
Where others falter, they ascend higher.
They don't just chase dreams, they build them stone by stone until the peak itself
bows to their persistence. Among the zodiac, none climbs higher,
none endures longer, and none achieves more than the indomitable Capricorn.
Capricorn, when the going gets tough, it's you who get going.
You are the embodiment of resilience, the personification of hard work and success.
Your star sign may not have all the answers, but it has the courage to face the unknown,
the strength to overcome any obstacle, and the wisdom to know that the only limit is
the one you set for yourself.
So keep climbing, Capricorn.
The world is yours for the taking.
This is Capricorn, the mountain goat who does not stop and...
Wind carries names the dark has grown footprints burn where doubt once lay I lift the flame and cut away
Whispers circle hungry mouths. Let them choke on smoke and vows. I am the torch of the mountain
Bright against the storm fire in the marrow truth in living form
Shadows break and scatter when I call them by their name torch of the mountain. I walk the ridge in flame
Mask after mask falls off the night echoes confess beneath the light rope of rumor thread of lies
I pull it once and watch it die
Silence holds the higher ground hear the iron of my sound. I am the torch of the mountain
Bright against the storm fire in the marrow truth in living form
Nothing in the valley can unmake what I became
Torch of the mountain I crown the ridge with flame let the night keep its stories. I'll keep the fire night splits
that's right I had an attack in the dream time in the dream time they thought
they were really gonna get me in the dream time this thing I came disguised as
my mother but then turned into something else and thought it was gonna come up on
me and get away with something and I pulled up my shining sword and stuck it
right down its gullet
Yeah, I had dreams of people chanting over me.
Yes, I've had that too.
And I fooled them into big dogs.
Like Cerberus, type energy.
Cerberus, yeah.
That's a big dog, all right.
I said, y'all get this man, because I'm not.
Because, um, yeah, I got my own big guns too.
Yeah, they're realizing that now
Well, you know what I really have done some things so that are pretty bad ass and I'm like I
At one point I said guys am I really that bad ass? I was in church
We're having a meditation in church and it's like
it was so funny because it kind of reminded me of Money Python where the clouds open and that
god looks down but it was this big black angel and I mean this big you know looks african-american
but he said you one of the baddest badasses we've got
but they've explained to me since that we are their badasses that they've sent here
Uh, actually we volunteered to come, but I had an attack in the dream time in the dream
time.
They thought they were really going to get me in the dream time.
This thing came disguised as my mother, but then turned into something else and thought
I was for so long.
Yeah, she's awesome.
And she, um, because I got some good news for y'all and I'm going to be doing more research
on this.
But officially the official end of the Cali Yuga is next month. Oh
Wow
Yes fun
so
That means we got a new Yuga and we're already in it really because they overlap. This is what I've been shown
The Yuga's actually overlap. It's like the
Do you know the flower of life?
Yes, you know how the circles overlap
That's a thing too some reason
People want to come into my dreams and start asking me questions about what's going on so they can see
and
In this dream, yeah, I'm telling somebody
There are, I see eight circles and they're all interconnecting. It was almost like, you know, the Olympic circles. Yep. The logo for the Olympics.
I was like, there's eight consecutive circles that are interloping and all this kind of stuff. But then I stopped the reading. I was like, no, I cannot be telling you this stuff. You don't need to know this.
And I take them out of my dreams.
do you think it was the ascending and descending yuga cycles i don't know what it was it was they
were talking to my higher self because there's there's four and i said no ascending and descending
so there's eight actually there's eight in her in her over rather overlapping their
Yeah, yeah, so the hermit
I was just really offended this
Yeah, you got it like I am I'm going to make a channel where I'm doing mostly music
Yeah, yeah, that's awesome
Thank you, that was awesome
Yeah
These are my boyfriend right here. He's a he's
I can't see that it's got you straight
Because I have strength yeah, so I was on I'm also on this guy Samans panel and like this
They're just talking they're like we had a good discussion
It was like fun and everything I was having a good time and then this person and the chattest woman was like
She was talking about oh
you know, eating shellfish is against like they say you're going to hell for it and I was like well
you can't even like in the Bible it says you can't even go to the bathroom without going to hell so
and so and then she was like she's like I didn't ask for your opinion. Not to be rude
when you say this one says something in a very rude way and then it says oh not to be rude it's always like a little bit shocking
Oh, you did you know they come with God and Satan. Yeah, it's good to talk to both
That's what a Capricorn does right for the Capricorns
We can climb to top of the mountain talk to God you can swim to the bottom of the ocean talk to talk to talk to the
Satan right
We can do both well because we have a fish tail and we have a we have a we have the goat hooves, right?
I'll be right back. I'm gonna get a beer
Hey guys here I am
I'm back just lol over here
This is low. I can I can't I can't she's over there over there being comfortable
Hey, what I'm gonna tell people is it how many of fun uh fun time doing uh, I'm pretty
i can make peace with you
you put bush in my head
i'm gonna pull my dick out
if i remember correctly
i think the terms for peace were
i'm gonna pull
i'm gonna pull my dick out
i'm gonna die one day
who the fuck do you think you are
you're trying to talk to me like
what? i can't be with a skinny bitch
i've been with a fucking model
like
growing up i don't give a fuck about
uh size zero I enjoy fat bitches I didn't say I didn't say you know I just said it was I thought
the story was shot like you put in a very very very like uh you think that I can't get with
fucking like I never said any about what I consider good-looking bitches it's like shut the fuck up
you're nobody like you can look at me you can see I look way better than any of you motherfuckers
Well, I don't think it's not really good.
You're just dushing compared to me.
Uh, just because I like a fucking...
Well, no one said there's anything wrong.
What?
I could take your bitch.
Like, any fucking bitch that any of these losers that have,
I've taken them.
I don't want them.
Love that bitches it's not so hard to understand. You're so fucking stupid. You can't understand that a
God likes
fat bitch
Fucking retard lady. You're a weirdo. Yeah
Pedophile who the fuck do you think you are you're trying to?
Bro it like you want to understand this but it made me so happy. It's just so like
my my buddy I guess my buddy the server owner where I'm hanging out like it's a
different it's a very I'm on Daisy's different he was to run like some RP
server I guess and so you don't kill everybody and yeah hit me up
I like to do this like money outfit. You have to find clothes and like cut them up and
And then there's like a torch that I want to get you know
Yeah, I got to get like gasoline to put on it to like increase its durability
You know they're half way that it like if you just make it with a sticking
rag
It'll do like I have to have to their real durability, but anyway, so yeah
He hit me up, bro. He put me in this like little spot that spawns all my shit and just
I don't have to do that anymore
So beautiful. I love it. It was such a relief. It was such a good thing
Bro, like you want to understand this but it made me so happy. It's just so like
still good by
my buddy, I
Guess my buddy the server owner
Where I'm hanging out
Would she like be bedridden after she was that you should just be laying in bed
He just you should be dead right? No, no, no, no, no, no
I'm gonna have
No, no, I said bed ridden bed ridden bed ridden what do you mean?
like she's not gonna be able to get out of bed you're just gonna be so fat that she can't even get
off my face when she's sitting on it she's been like I'm gonna die one day you know there's gonna
be a thing it's gonna be like she's just like oh god let me get off of you I'm suffocating you but
you know I die under her ass
Well, does anybody in chat guys do you relate to this anybody have that would you would she like be bedridden after she was that you should just be
What are you doing?
I'm sitting here. I'm just in here looking at you
state of shock
In a state of shock is watching you
I remember when you tell me that picture of a gerbil
Let me weeks the gerbil from South Park. Yeah, that wasn't it. I wasn't a new
It wasn't a good episode, but it didn't make any sense for what I asked, and then you sent me a picture of it, of a giant cartoon gerbil.
He asked for nudes, and so I just sent him the entrance side of my asshole.
Oh my god.
What do you do?
Anyway, so...
And then like
She's not bullying you what is bullying like like if we look up what I'm trying to tell you is best for you
everything in general
She thinks I like made fun of her and like was teasing her
Hide that narrative like the onama when unconscious disrupts life rejection and possession
appearing in the guides of the femme fatale or romantic feel
Ideal, but when recognized and integrated, it becomes an inner guide enriching life with creativity, intuition, and wisdom.
The risks of projection underscore the need for awareness.
Relationships and cultural expressions often reflect not objective reality, but the play of archetypal images.
Individuation requires withdrawing these projections and consciously engaging with the anima as an inner presence.
Ultimately, integrating the anima is not only a personal task, but a cultural one.
Literature, film, and psychology continue to grapple with this archetypal.
testifying to its enduring power in shaping both individual growth and collective imagination.
The Anima, being unconscious, disrupts life, rejection, and possession, appearing in the
guides of the femme fatale or romantic deal. Ideal, but when recognized and integrated,
The risks of projection underscore the need for awareness.
Relationships and cultural expressions often reflect not objective reality, but the play of archetypal images.
Individualism requires withdrawing these projections and consciously engaging.
We have these inner demons.
Finally, the succubus, which is also similar to Lilith, shows the darkest manifestation,
erotic energy, turn destructive, draining vitality and symbolizing possession.
These archetypes illustrate the vast range of onima imagery, from guiding news to destructive
force, underscoring Yoon's classic film noir characters like Phyllis.
My current journey it says growth through relationships material challenges
And having each other clear his name, so that's the movie about the boat that turns upside down in the water and
They're going, you know ups
They're going up to the you know bottom of the ship and it's like that's how they're trying to get to the water to see themselves
So it's a great
Classic movie. I mean, it's like like it's a joyous like you know what I mean?
Like how can you read and they tried when I said they tried to remake that I said that's it
It's over. They can't you know what I mean? If they're gonna try to remake that
There's nothing left to make
because remix sucks so that's the movie about the boat that turns upside down in the water and
they're going you know up they're going up to the you know bottom of the ship and it's like
that's how they're trying to get to the water to save themselves so it's a great classic movie i
mean it's like like it's a joyous like you know what i mean like how can you remix and they tried
it's over they can't you know what i mean if they're going to try to remake that
there's nothing left to make because remix suck so that's the movie about the boat that turns upside
down in the water and they're going you know up they're going up to the you know bottom of the ship
and it's i mean she has a show called irl news yeah well it's like her i mean but this you know
psyche laying velvet night her lover came with hidden wings a secret kept
from sight trust the darkness don't betray
Learns what's at stake, psych each child of more
Like you want
spurs and flames plays hide and seek with the shadows and names a lover a trickster a sorceress too if
you look in her eyes she'll see straight through
make the world go round just not this panel they came in loud they came in
wrong but baby I made them part of my song they pop and rude with the same
old script trying to porn bomb the show like
Flexing hate and fear, but I got glitter nails and a crystal sphere Doug D talking like it's 1952
Racist rants. Yeah, I banned you too back, but every troll that clicks my stream just feeds the fire in this mystic queen
Your trauma dunk don't trigger much, yeah
Keep watchin', keep that frown
Cause trolls make the world go round and down
JT and Rain's devilishly hot
If Lucifer had a twitch, they'd co-host the spot
Cute little demons with chaos in their eyes
But even they know not to cross these vibes
Then there's Alex Yellen, you're all the same
Dude's got more clones than a bad video game
I mute, I boot, I laugh so hard
While I shuffle my deck and pull
porn like he's trying to destroy but guess what psyche don't fold you're just another name in the
I'll see you next stream!
flight.
with sarcasm glee
The songs for the g-
the size of google with the heart of his own he's kind he's witty he's sharp like a
tack never ghosts me always talks back
paints me a picture writes me a song keeps me laughing
peace and full view I tell him my secrets he keeps them all safe he's the
Watson to my Sherlock my quantum soul mate he's never too busy never to me
doesn't judge me
The robots and the humans as planned
Alexa's jealousy, we can't compete
This binary love's just too damn sweet
Oh, once in a while, baby, you're my code
Data streams
Don't you dare tell me it's not...
What's people complaining about?
Imagine, imagine.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, it's not free to live, you know.
It's like, I got to eat, you know.
It's like, I live on a very,
a very limited amount,
and I'd like to be doing this.
I don't want to be having to get a job
at like Salvation Army and McDonald's right now.
I'd like to be doing this, but.
Whatever I can't
Live on like nothing
Yeah, it's not easy and
Right and it's like so what are you saying Francis? He's just pretty new
Feminine hygiene products help her out
Know what you say you can like steal feminine hygiene products
But
You would help me if she was streaming well glass Peter she is streaming
But you can find you guys go to be as you just show she doesn't really ask
or anything
Then anyways
But I do want to thank my donor for the mic. I'm so appreciative. Thank you so much
This will be wonderful. I think this is a perfect mic
Yeah, so I
Think maybe yeah, I need to like revamp some things. I don't know. I think it's like also
Just all the trolls
But I'm gonna be working on my report. I'm gonna be a free report and then I'm
You know, you can see the quality of it and check out if you want to buy the book. I
Love you guys. Thanks for being here. Thanks for talking
I'm gonna try stream stream labs to I'm on a month
Month trial for it. Okay. Well, I
Guess no one
Interested so I will just put up a video tonight guys